alomone.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy

 Alomone Labs Ltd. ("Alomone" or "We") knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously.  Alomone has created this privacy statement ("Statement") in order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.  
By accessing the Alomone’s website at [ **www.alomone.com**](http://www.alomone.com/), including all related pages ("Site"), including any subscription based features or services offered by Alomone through the Site or through info.Alomone.com (collectively, the "Service"), you are accepting the practices outlined in this Statement.

**1\. What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?**

This Statement covers Alomone’s collection and use of personal information that Alomone gathers when you are on the Site and when you use the Service.  
This Statement does not apply to the practices of third parties that Alomone does not own or control, or to individuals that Alomone does not employ or manage.  
For avoidance of doubt, this Statement does not apply to any third party information gathered by Alomone's subscribers (i.e., information about customers of Alomone subscribers) and submitted by them to the Service for use in connection with their marketing campaigns and other promotional activities ("Customer Data"). Alomone will not review, share, distribute, print, or reference any such Customer Data except as provided in the Service Agreement or as may be required by law. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Customer Data may at times be viewed or accessed by Alomone for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issue, or for investigating a suspected violation of the Service Agreement, or as may be required by law.

**2\. What Personal Information About Customers Does Alomone Collect?**

Our primary goal in collecting information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We collect the following types of information from our customers:  
**Information You Provide to Us:**  
Alomone collects identifying information when you visit the Site (including, without limitation, any Alomone.com web pages or landing pages), and when you enter promotions or contests. For example, we may require customers who register to use the website to give us the following personal information: their name, Company name, address, phone number, and e-mail address, and financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number.  When you initially express interest obtaining additional information about our products, or when you register for the Service, we may also ask for additional types personal information, such as title, department name, fax number, or additional company information. We may also request demographic information and unique identifiers in order to provide you with a more personalized experience or verify your passwords.  
All financial and billing information that we collect from you is used for billing you for the products you purchase. Such billing information is not used by Alomone for marketing or promotional purposes. Alomone may use a third-party intermediary to manage the credit card and billing processing. This intermediary is solely a link in the distribution chain, and is not permitted to store, retain, or use the information provided, except for the sole purpose of credit card and billing processing.  
**Automatic Information:**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via our website. Alomone automatically receives and records certain "traffic data" on our server logs including your IP address, Alomone cookie information, the page you requested, and your communications and interactions with other site registrants. Alomone uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the Service.  
We automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and use of components of our Service. We may use this information to provide research, advice and information, including, without limitation, for benchmarking purposes (e.g. we may publish an industry white paper that uses data collected through the use of our website). This data is only used in the aggregate. This type of collective data also enables us to figure out how often customers use our website so we can make the website appealing to as many customers as possible.  
We also collect and use information for internal purposes. For example, if you are a registered user of the Alomone's website, we may keep records in your account history of your complaints about our products, in order to improve our technical support service in the future.  
**E-mail Communications:**  
We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from Alomone if your computer supports this type of program, in order to help us make e-mails more interesting and helpful. We may also send out emails with information regarding Alomone or our partners including promotions and events. Customers can opt out of being contacted by us by sending an email to [ **info@alomone.com**](mailto:info@alomone.com).  
If a user elects to use our referral features for informing a friend about our Site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Alomone will automatically send the friend an email on behalf of the user who made the referral, inviting such friend to visit the Site.  
**Information From Other Sources:**  
For purposes such as improving personalization of our Service, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.  

**3.What about Cookies?**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. Alomone employs cookies in order for its server to recognize a return visitor as a unique user. The cookies placed by the Alomone server are readable only by Alomone, and cookies cannot access, read or modify any other data on a computer.  
The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of Alomone's most attractive features.  

**4\. Will Alomone Share Any of the Information it Receives?**

Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only with entities that are controlled or controlled by or under common control of Alomone, and as described below:  
**Agents:**  
We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and may need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples may include removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. We may also provide your personal information to agents who will use it to verify aggregate usage data that we provide to our partners. In all cases where we share your information with such agents, we explicitly require the agent to acknowledge and adhere to Alomone's privacy and customer data handling policies.  
**Business Transfers:**  
In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets or businesses. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Alomone, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, customer information would be one of the assets that are transferred.  
**Protection of Alomone and Others:**  
We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Alomone, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  
**With Your Consent:**  
Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties.  

**5\. Is Information About Me Secure?**

All customer information collected and stored by Alomone is maintained in a secure corporate data center and/or otherwise subject to best practices access protection. Only employees who need customer information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.  

**6\. How Can I Correct or Remove Information About Me?**

If you feel that any personal information about you that has been collected and stored by Alomone might be wrong, or you would like for us to remove you from our systems, please notify us at [ **info@Alomone.com**](mailto:info@Alomone.com) so that we may correct or delete the information.  

**7\. What Choices Do I Have?**

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to make a purchase or take advantage of certain Alomone features.  
As explained earlier, the "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if you do not enable cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features.  

**8\. Can Children Use Alomone's services?**

Our site and the use of services made available through Alomone are not intended for children under the age of 18. Alomone does not knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 18 and believes that children of any age should get their parents' consent before giving out any personal information. If you believe that we have mistakenly or unintentionally collected such information through our website, please notify us at [ **info@Alomone.com**](mailto:info@Alomone.com) so that we may immediately delete the information from our servers.  

**9\. Conditions of Use**

If you decide to visit the Alomone Site, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Israeli law.  

**10\. Third Party Sites**

Other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Alomone site. These other websites are not under Alomone control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by Alomone of those other websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Alomone site are not covered by this Privacy Statement, and Alomone is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.  

**11\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Alomone may amend this Privacy Policy. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will notify you by posting the revised notice on our Site or sending you an email so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.  

**12\. Questions or Concerns**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at Alomone site, please email [ **info@Alomone.com**](mailto:info@Alomone.com). Your privacy is important to us and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

**Privacy Policy Effective Date: 3/6/2013**
